<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Smart Agriculture</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="title_more">More</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_account">Account</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="nav_agro_news">Agro News</string>
    <string name="nav_daily_vegetable_market">Daily Veg Market</string>
    <string name="nav_about_us">About us</string>
    <string name="nav_share_app">Share app</string>
    <string name="nav_login">Login</string>
    <string name="nav_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="client_id">114205616348-9qbjqom0cshitht92b7n8ns3ro9pp1r4.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">210573751098791</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb210573751098791</string>
    <string name="profile_image_desc">profile image</string>
    <string name="username">username</string>
    <string name="email">email</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="btn_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="about_us">ABOUT US</string>
    <string name="share_app">SHARE APP</string>
    <string name="text_contact_us">Contact Us:</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate Us</string>
    <string name="login_click">Click here to login Smart Agriculture</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="dashboard_desc">You can perform crud operations in this dashboard which includes adding agriculture news, information about agriculture, and many more things</string>
    <string name="operations_dashboard_desc">You can click on the specific image button to perform operations.</string>
    <string name="add_news">ADD NEWS</string>
    <string name="update_news">UPDATE NEWS</string>
    <string name="add_info">ADD INFO</string>
    <string name="update_info">UPDATE INFO</string>
    <string name="change_image">CHANGE IMAGE</string>
    <string name="action_edit">EDIT</string>
    <string name="action_remove">DELETE</string>
    <string name="add_agriculture_news">Add AgrIculture News :</string>
    <string name="add_agriculture_information">Add Agriculture Information</string>
    <string name="ekantipur">ekantipur</string>
    <string name="news_source">News Source</string>
    <string-array name="source_list">
        <item>ekantipur</item>
        <item>krishi post</item>
        <item>kisan aawaj</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="register_as_farmer_details">
        If You are farmer and your want to sell then you can register as a farmer.
        If you register as a farmer then you have many features available which are as below:\n\n

        1. You can unlock message us directly feature and contact us via app.\n
        2. You can post your product details like product images, product description, product price per unit etc.\n
        3. You can sell via app using Sell your product option which is appear on "more" page after registration as farmer.\n\n

        CLICK ON THE IMAGE BELOW TO REGISTER AS A FARMER
    </string>
    <string name="_2_user_messages">2. User Messages :</string>
    <string name="jilla">जिल्ला *</string>
    <string name="gaupalika_text">नगरपालिका/गाँउपालिका *</string>
    <string name="mb_text">मोबाईल नम्बर *</string>
    <string name="reg_text">Register as a Farmer (कृषकको लागी दर्ता गर्नुहोस )</string>
    <string name="reg_farmer">Register Farmer(कृषकको दर्ता)</string>
    <string name="version">Version</string>
    <string name="our_services">Our Services :</string>
    <string name="_1_hyperlink">1. Hyperlink</string>
    <string name="_2_register_as_a_farmer">2. Register as a Farmer</string>
    <string name="image_news">image news</string>
    <string name="image_vegmarket">image_vegMarket</string>
    <string name="img_weather">img_weather</string>
    <string name="image_register_farmer">image_register_farmer</string>
    <string name="product_title">Product Title...</string>
    <string name="product_price">Product Price</string>
    <string name="add_product">ADD PRODUCT</string>
    <string name="update_product">UPDATE PRODUCT</string>
    <string name="del_or_ed">Edit or Delete product</string>
    <string name="product_image">PRODUCT IMAGE</string>
    <string name="image_description">Image Description</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fullscreen">FullscreenActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="stock_name">अर्डर गर्दा कुल स्टक भन्दा कम अर्डर गर्नुहोला । जुन एकाइ मा कुल स्टक रखिएको छ त्यही एकाइ मा आफुलाई चहिने अर्डर राख्नुहोला । </string>
    <string name="total_stock">Total Stock : </string>
    <string name="your_orders">Your stock :</string>
    <string name="edit_your_orders">How much/many you want to get(unit)</string>
    <string name="send_req">SEND ORDER REQUEST</string>
    <string name="dialog_message_order">Are you sure you want to delete this order? This process cannot be undone.</string>
    <string name="otp_confirmation_dialog">OTP CONFIRMATION DIALOG</string>
    <string name="register_as_farmer">VERIFY AND REGISTER AS FARMER</string>
    <string name="enter_otp">ENTER OTP</string>
    <string name="desc_reg_farmer">Kindly login through Facebook or Google to authenticate first for registering as a Farmer !</string>
    <string name="theme_app">स्मार्ट कृषि स्मार्ट किसान</string>
    <string name="theme_home">अब कृषि सामाग्री मगाउनु होस सिधै कृषक बाट</string>
    <string name="more_options">More Options</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="farmer_help">After transferring Normal users to farmer users, they get many more features: \n
        1. Farmer user can post their product regarding agriculture. \n
        2. Farmer use can see their posted product inside product dashboard. \n
        3. They can edit/update and delete their posted product inside the product dashboard. \n
        4. They can see their profile inside the product dashboard and edit their profile. \n
        5. They can see their total sales, total orders, total completed orders, and total pending orders below their profile. \n
        6. They can see the order dashboard button below to their details. \n
        7. After clicking on the order dashboard, the farmer can see their pending and completed orders in the list and their pages.\n
    </string>

    <string name="farmerRegHelp">For farmer registration, there is an option inside more option in Bottom navigation.\n
        You can see the Image Button register as farmer.\n
        after clicking on the image button, you can see that there is a form field to register as a farmer.\n
        It needs :
        1. Province \n
        2.  District \n
        3. Municipality|subMunicipality \n
        4. Mobile Number \n
        After clicking on the Register as farmer button, the user can see the dialog and it needs OTP to verify your mobile number,\n
        after entering OTP which is 6 digit pin, users mobile number is successfully verified and now farmer user have more features compared to a normal user.\n
    </string>
    <string name="order_help">For ordering the product posted by a normal user,\n
    1. First you can go to the product details of any product.\n
    2. On the product details page, you can see the ORDER AND REQUEST button.\n
    3. After clicking on that order and request button, a dialog box is appeared.\n
    4. There is edit Text in the dialog, you have to enter stock less than the stock posted by the farmer and in the exact unit posted by the farmer.\n
    5. After entering the correct stock you need, you can press the send image button and your order is requested. \n
    </string>
    <string name="user_help">Normal users or buyers can easily install smart agriculture apps from Google Play Store.\n
        After Installing,
he/she can see the product on the home screen posted by the farmer. He/she can click on the product for product details.\n
* Normal users can easily, send an order request directly to the farmer.\n
* There is more option in the bottom navigation, you can see many more features there,\n
You can read the news regarding agriculture by clicking agriculture news posted by admin users,\n
You can view weather information which helps both farmers and normal users.\n
You can view market information that shows market values (eg. Kalimati) for vegetable stuff.\n
You can see the many information regarding seeds and plants in the information section.\n
/n/n
Note: Normal users can easily transfer to Farmer users anytime they want.\n
    </string>
    <string name="user_reg_help">For registering as a normal user, you can see the login button in the menu drawable or from the account option in Bottom Navigation.\n
        There is an option to log in: \n
        1. You can login via Your Google account or Your Facebook Account.\n
        2. After login, You have to feature like requesting an order inside the product description\n
    </string>
</resources>